// Answer text must be under 25 characters otherwise they'll be truncated
// Answer value but be the lowecase LETTER of the correct answer (a, b, c, or d)
module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'What the average amount of time a person will spend at a red light?',
      a: 'two weeks',
      b: 'one month',
      c: 'six months',
      d: 'one year',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'What color was the first orange(the fruit)?',
      a: 'orange',
      b: 'red',
      c: 'green',
      d: 'pink',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'When was the first computer invented?',
      a: '1930s',
      b: '1940s',
      c: '1890s',
      d: '1960s',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is a Pringle?',
      a: 'a chip',
      b: 'a fry',
      c: 'a crinkle',
      d: 'a crisp',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the technical term for this symbol: # ',
      a: 'Octothorpe',
      b: 'Hashtag',
      c: 'Number Sign',
      d: 'Numerical Symbol',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "M&M? stand for? (yes, the candy)',
      a: 'It stands for nothing',
      b: 'Melty and Milky',
      c: 'Melts in your mouth',
      d: 'Mars and Murrie',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is a baby puffin is called?',
      a: 'puffy',
      b: 'puffler',
      c: 'puffling',
      d: 'lil puf',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'How many Grammys did Elivs win?',
      a: '3',
      b: '5',
      c: '11',
      d: '14',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'What was the first soft drink in space?',
      a: 'Coca-Cola',
      b: 'Sprite',
      c: 'Pepsi',
      d: 'Fanta',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is average number of grapes that go into a bottle of wine? (hint: 2.6 lbs)',
      a: '350',
      b: '500',
      c: '700',
      d: '950',
      answer: 'c'
    }
  ]
};